Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, ca. 1950s-2000; I.
  - 35mm Negatives, ca. 1950s- 2000; 1.
    - 1972
      - Koppers: Petrolia Plant, March 16, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 68)
      - Boy Scouts, March 20, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 69)
      - Feldman and Kahn, R.P.C. Electronics, April 1, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 70-76, 78-81, 83-86)
      - Koppers: Walman Foundation, Columbus, Ohio; AWUF Virginia Homes, April 4, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2-5)
      - Toledo Laminated Beam, April 17, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6, 8, 10, 12, 14, 16, 18-19)
      - Phil Elbing Children, May 1, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20-37)
      - Mr. Roger's Neighborhood (TV Set), Mathew and Lady Aberlin, May 15, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - Koppers: Susquehanna Plant Dedication, May 15, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 47-51)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann; Petrolia Pennsylvania Reactor, May 25, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 67-68)
      - Three Rivers Arts Festival, May 26, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 69-77)
      - Wolman Foundation, Cincinnati, Ohio, AWWF Cincinnati, June 9, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 78-81)
      - Koppers: Kauffmann "Treasure Lake", June 13, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - Computer School, July 4, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 3-7)
      - Lando, Vince Hanpatty, "Magnetics," Studio Job, July 7, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, 1901 Koppers Building Public Relations Department, July 28, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 10-14, 16)
      - Koppers: Washington Plaza Pool, Sam Kauffmann, July 28, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, "Koppers Employees", August 14, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 25-35)
      - Koppers, August 22, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 46-47)
      - Koppers: Railroad Ties, August 28, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 48-49)
      - Koppers, September 25, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 50-52)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Stan Kent, November 1, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 54-69)
      - Koppers: AWWF Bankert, November 4, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 70-75)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, November 9, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1-11)
      - Wood, November 30, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - 1973
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, January 11, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
      - Machines, January 11, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 17-19)
      - Koppers, January 16, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 25-26)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, February 15, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 29-32)
      - Koppers, February 15, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 33-35)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, February 16, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 36-42)
      - Guilbert Long, February 24, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Fieldman and Kahn, Stan Kent (WWSW), March 2, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 44-58)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, March 14, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 63-64)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, March 24, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
      - Koppers, March 29, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
      - Railroad Timbers, April 5, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, April 5, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 13-16)
      - Railroad, April 12, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, Playground, April 13, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 20-25)
      - Roof, April 19, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26-27)
      - Camping in the Woods (Boy Scouts), April 20, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Lando, Babette Mandel, April 28, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 29-35)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, May 3, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Ed Gibbs Sailing, May 7, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 37-38, 40-41)
      - Chickens and Old Car, May 7, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 39, 42, 44)
      - Koppers: Jim Pisarcik, May 11, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 46-48)
      - Koppers: Wrenton Coles Oven, May 11, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 57-58)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, Pittsburgh History and Landmarks, June 25, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Stan Kent, Arnheim Neely, June 26, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7-19)
      - Handicapped Kids, June 28, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20-23)
      - Koppers, July 9, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 24-26)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Stan Kent, WWSEV, July 12, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 27-30)
      - Koppers Polos, July 19, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 33-38)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), August 15, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 40-41, 43)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, August 21, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 52, 54,56,58, 60, 62, 64, 66, 70)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, August 30, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1-10)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, September 6, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, September 11, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
      - Wood, September 17, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26-29)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, September 19, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), September 22, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 31-35)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, October 19, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 63-64)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, October 22, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 65-71)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), October 29, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 72)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), October 29, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2, 4, 6, 8, 10)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, November 1, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
      - Disc Jockey with Beard, November 7, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, November 16, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 22,24,26)
      - Harold Betters at Piano Group (Mat as Jesus in School Play), December 19, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 29-35)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, December 21, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, December 27, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 37-38)
      - Social Security Administration: Shoe Store, May 21, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1-8, 15)
      - Europe: Milan, WABCO, Inside Train, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
      - Europe: Scraper, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 5-9)
      - Europe: Hannover, Germany, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10-21)
      - Europe: Paris, France, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
      - Europe: Turin, Italy, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 24-29)
      - Europe: Lausanne, Switzerland, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 30-34)
      - Europe: Nuremburg, Germany, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 35-37)
      - Europe: DiMetal, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 38-50)
      - Europe: Subway Milan, Italy, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - 1974
      - Koppers, January 15, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 39-40)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), January 22, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 46-53)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Stan Kent, February 4, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 75-77)
      - The Cullough Communications, February 13, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7-19)
      - K.M. and G., Dennis Casey, February 15, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 20, 23-24, 26, 28, 30)
      - Nuclear Plant and Fish, February 15, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - People in Living Room, March 4, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Curt Miller, Burson-Marsteller, March 18, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 42-43)
      - Koppers: Boonesboro, Kentucky, Huck DeVenzio, April 2, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 46, 48, 50-51)
      - Koppers: Mercury Light Riser, Huck DeVenzio, April 3, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - Koppers: Explorers Congress, Huck DeVenzio, April 4, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 57-63)
      - Koppers: Environmental Systems (EEC Plant), Huck DeVenzio, April 5, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 66-67)
      - University of Pittsburgh: Mollie De Carlo, Commencement, April 28, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 69-76)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), May 5, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Koppers, May 8, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, May 13, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 32-37)
      - Charlotte Birnbaum, May 20, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 38-39)
      - Koppers: John Boal, May 21, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 40-43)
      - Colie Owen, June 12, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 59-60)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, "United Way", June 20, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 63-65)
      - Koppers: "United Way", July 2, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 68-69)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, "United Way", July 5, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 70)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, "United Way", July 15, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 71)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, July 19, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 72-74)
      - Koppers, July 19, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 75)
      - Koppers, July 23, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 82-83)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), July 23, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
      - Sautel, Tom Winslow, Computer School, July 29, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 11-16)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, "Politics", August 5, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 17-20)
      - Koppers, August 30, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 31-32)
      - Mellon Bank: Bill Blansett, "Poetry", September 5, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 33-39)
      - Mellon Bank: Bill Blansett, September 18, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 40-48)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), "Light Poles", October 3, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 54)
      - Koppers: John Boal, "Factory Scene", October 4, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 59)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, "David and Elkins College", October 11, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 65-77)
      - Bob O'Gara, Health-O-Rama, October 26, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3-6)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, "Noctane Umbrella", November 14, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 19-22)
      - Deck, December 13, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - 1975
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, Christmas Tree, January 3, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 30-32)
      - Koppers, January 9, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), "Florida", January 15, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 34-38)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, "Mr. Capone", January 21, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 55-56)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, "Monroeville Research", January 27, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 57-60)
      - Dave Milton, Golden Theatre, February 10, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 61)
      - Koppers, February 11, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 62)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, Peppermint Patty, February 14, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 65)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), "Florida", February 24, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 66-72)
      - Woodplant, February 24, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 82)
      - Personal, Engelmeier, March 4, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
      - Lecture, March 27, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3-6)
      - Robert Fletcher, March 30, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Mellon Bank: African American Employees at Bank, Bill Blansett, April 17, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 13-16)
      - Koppers: Boy Scouts, April 24, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 17-22)
      - University of Pittsburgh: Mollie De Carlo, Commencement, April 27, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 23-31)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, Steak and Ale, Fireproof Plywood, Atlanta Georgia, May 17, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 46-50)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, Chicago, June 5, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 58-60)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, Albany, June 9, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 78)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, Fitness, June 12, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1-7)
      - Mellon Bank, July 8, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 8-9)
      - Koppers: Helen Zimecki, Project: Improvement, July 22, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 17-21)
      - Koppers, August 13, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 34-36)
      - Koppers: Helen Zimecki, August 21, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 40-48)
      - Koppers: Helen Zimecki, J and L Aliquippa, August 28, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 52-54, 57)
      - Koppers: Helen Zimecki, "Spatz", September 4, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 58-59)
      - Koppers, September 5, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 60-61)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, Wood Things, September 7, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - Koppers: Plant MGR AD with Firestand Wood, N.C.X., October 1, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 1, 3)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Iriax Dome, October 17, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, Harmarville, Rehab Center, October 21, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Annapolis Maryland, October 27, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 43-46)
      - Koppers, November 20, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 52, 57-58)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), N.C.X., Virginia, December 2, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 66-67)
      - Mellon Bank, December 5, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 82-87)
      - Koppers, December 16, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, December 19, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, Executive Portraits, December 29, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3-7)
      - Koppers, December 29, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 8-11)
      - Church, October 13, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 64)
      - Dancers at a Party, October 13, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - 1976
      - Koppers, January 20, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Acidbar, February 3, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, Executive Portraits, February 6, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 18-20)
      - Koppers: Res. Frances, March 1, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Beechwood Court Yard Walkway, March 25, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 49-50)
      - Koppers, March 29, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 51-52)
      - Koppers, April 1, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 53)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, April 15, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 57-59)
      - Koppers, April 27, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 79)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Atlanta, May 3, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Chicago and Columbian Wood, May 10, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 18-20)
      - Koppers, July 1976 (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - Koppers, August 2, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 64-66)
      - Wood Construction, August 25, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
      - Koppers, September 15, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Koppers, September 25, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 36-39)
      - Koppers: Girl in Lab, October 6, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Koppers: Weirton Coke Plant, October 27, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 46-47)
      - Koppers: Theim Co., November 10, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 51-52)
      - Mellon Bank, November 27, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 63-66)
      - Koppers: Barb Portrait, December 12, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 70-71)
    - 1977
      - Bud's Christmas in House, Rick Levenison, The Band, January 17, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Koppers: Barb Portrait, February 1, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Pennsylvania Association for the Blind, February 21, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Portraits, Students in Lab, March 10, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 9-17)
      - University of Pittsburgh Commencement, April 24, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 34-44)
      - Koppers, July 20, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 50)
      - Robert Kohler, August 12, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 58-61, 68)
      - Koppers: Sentry Insurance Building, October 25, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 61-65)
      - Koppers, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7-10)
      - Two Men in an Office, October 17, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Koppers, October 29, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12-16)
      - Koppers, November 16, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 17-22)
      - Koppers: Titus Products, Houston Texas, December 2, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 23-26)
      - Koppers: Cumberland Circle, December 8, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 38-39)
      - Koppers, December 16, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 38-39)
      - Koppers: Lander and Sprout, October 2, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 49-51)
      - Koppers, October 20, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 53-58)
    - 1978
      - Koppers, January 9, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1-2, 4-6)
      - Koppers: Mr. Cowles, January 25, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
      - Koppers: Little Rock, January 30, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9-13)
      - Koppers: N.C.X. Wood, February 15, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 23-25)
      - Koppers: Railwood Sawmill, March 3, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 30-33)
      - Koppers: Houston, Dallas, April 12, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 45-47)
      - Koppers: Television Executives, April 28, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 48-50)
      - Susie and Trophy, May 1, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 51)
      - Koppers, May 5, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 52-63)
      - Sam Kauffmann, Denver, Girl on Plane, May 9, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 64)
      - Koppers: Fletcher Byrom Lecture, May 10, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 65-66)
      - Koppers: Chicken Coops, July 19, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5-6)
      - The White Hawk Sailboat, July 24, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 14-18)
      - Koppers: Florida Projects, December 18, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 26-29)
      - BMX Mat, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 30-40)
    - 1979
      - Boston Marathon: 3 Koppers Employees Enter, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 41-44)
      - Koppers, December 19, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 55-57)
    - 1980
      - J. Panzar, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 58-61)
      - Chatham College: Women's Basketball, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Koppers, January 25, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 24-30)
      - T. Barr Chatham Commencement, February 1980 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Disney World, February 27, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 24-36)
      - Chatham College: Basketball, March 3, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 37-40)
      - Chatham College: Snow, March 19, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 41-42)
      - BMX, March 25, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 43-47)
      - BMX, April 1, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 48-53)
      - Classrooms, April 4, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 54-62)
      - Classrooms, April 4, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 1-8)
      - Koppers: Montreal, Canada, May 23, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 23-29)
      - Chatham College: Graduation, May 28, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 30-34)
      - Bicycles, May 28, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 35-39)
      - BMX, June 12, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 40-47)
      - BMX, July 8, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 48-55)
      - Eye and Ear Hospital, September 1980 (Box 40, Folder 56)
      - National Champ, September 8, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 57-67)
      - John Serefini (Client), Stephenson Agency, 5th and Wood, September 16, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 68)
      - Cyclist, November 4, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 69)
      - Koppers, November 21, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 70-71)
    - 1981
      - Koppers: E.I. 1600, May 6, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 72-73)
      - BMX, December 21, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 74-80)
    - 1982
      - BMX, March 17, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
      - Koppers: Bicycles, May 18, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5-7)
      - BMX: Dayton, Ohio, July 1982 (Box 41, Folder 8-12)
    - 1987
      - Koppers, June 24, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 14-17)
      - Koppers: Concrete Ties, November 30, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 18-26)
      - Koppers: Spatz, January 9, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 81)
    - 1988
      - Portrait, September 29, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 27-28)
    - 1989
      - Koppers: Roofing, May 31, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 29-32)
      - Koppers: Ford Romeo, July 19, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 33-37)
      - Koppers: Detroit Roofs, August 10, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 38-50)
      - Mellon Bank, October 26, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 51-58)
      - Hickson Corporation: Charleston, November 6, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 59-62)
    - 1990
      - Hickson Corporation: Color Deck, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 63)
      - Thrift Drug Classic, ca. 1990s (Box 3, Folder 40-41)
    - 1991
      - Thrift Drug Classic: Sophie, Eric and Bud, Start Line, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 64-66)
    - 1992
      - Thrift Drug Classic, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 68-69)
      - Witalis Burke: #6725, July 7, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 70-72)
      - Archadeck: Decks, August 31, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - Hickson Corporation, October 29, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 74-75)
      - Hickson Corporation: Huck DeVenzio, October 30, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1-8)
    - 1993
      - Hickson Corporation, September 10, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 9-11)
      - Hickson Corporation, September 24, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12-20)
      - Hickson Corporation, October 26, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 26-32)
      - Alcoa: Holiday Party/Meeting, December 12, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 38-42)
    - 1994
      - Opera, March 1, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 43-57)
      - Portrait of Ann, March 20, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 58-59)
      - Hickson Corporation, April 22, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 60-64)
      - Hickson Corporation, April 28, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 65-75)
      - Alcoa, Chairman, Paul O'Neil, Family at Home on Christmas, December 31, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 76)
      - Alcoa, July 27, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, Joyce Saltzman, August 2, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
      - Alcoa, August 5, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 7-9)
      - Alcoa, August 23, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 10-12)
      - Hickson Corporation, April 28, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 13-20)
      - Hickson Corporation, May 10, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 21-30)
      - Archadeck, June 2, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 31-32)
      - Archadeck, June 23, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 33-34)
      - Alcoa, September 9, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 35-38)
      - Alcoa, September 22, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 39-43)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, October 14, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 44-47)
      - Alcoa, October 18, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 48-50)
      - Alcoa, October 21, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 51-52)
      - Alcoa: Atlanta Pics, Greg Mims, November 9, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 53)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, November 10, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 54-56)
      - Alcoa: Joyce Saltzman, November 16, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 57-58)
      - Alcoa: Joyce Saltzman, November 18, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 59-62)
      - Alcoa: Joyce Saltzman, Laura Venchesi, December 19, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 63-64)
      - Alcoa: Shadyside Hospital, December 16, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 65-66)
    - 1995
      - Thrift Drug Classic, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 67)
      - Alcoa, Sunil Vora, January 12, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 68-69)
      - Alcoa, January 17, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 70-72)
      - Alcoa, January 18, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 73-76)
      - Alcoa, January 26, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 77-78)
      - Alcoa: Hoops, Joyce Seltzman, Greg Mims, February 9, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 79-86)
      - Al Post/ Posti and Associates, March 4, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
      - Alcoa, March 5, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
      - Alcoa, March 21, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 8-9)
      - Alcoa, March 23, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Alcoa, March 30, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Alcoa, April 11, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Alcoa, April 18, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 13-17)
      - Alcoa, April 24, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 18-21)
      - Hickson Corporation, May 30, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 22-30)
      - Alcoa, June 9, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Alcoa, June 14, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 32-36)
      - Alcoa, June 20, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Koppers: Tar, June 28, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Alcoa, July 12, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 39-40)
      - Alcoa, October 18, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 41-42)
      - Alcoa, October 23, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 43-45)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, December 22, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - 1996
      - Thrift Drug Classic, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 47-54)
      - Alcoa, January 4, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 55-56)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, January 21, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 57-58)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, January 26, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 59-62)
      - Alcoa, February 1, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 63-64)
      - Alcoa, February 7, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 65-68)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, March 4, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 69)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, March 12, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 70)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, April 3, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 71-72)
      - Alcoa, April 15, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 73-74)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, April 26, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 75-80)
      - Alcoa, May 13, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 81-82)
      - Alcoa: Greg Mims, June 3, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 83)
      - Alcoa, June 7, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 84-85)
      - Smaller Manufacturer Council (SMC), July 2, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 86)
      - Alcoa, August 12, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 87-89)
      - Alcoa: Day of Caring, Ligonier Boy Scout Camp, September 19, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 6-9)
      - Alcoa, September 20, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 10-11)
      - Alcoa, September 26, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 12-17)
      - Koppers: Roofing, October 8, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 18-20)
      - Hickson Corporation, October 15, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 21-23)
    - 1997
      - African Dancers, Greg Mims, June 28, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 24-25)
    - 1998
      - Koppers, July 1, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
      - Great Race, September 25, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Race Across America, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - 1999
      - Koppers: Roof, September 9, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 32-33)
      - Ren School Roof, September 23, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - Hickson Corporation, October 1, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 36-40)
    - 2000
      - Koppers: Balcas, September 12, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - 2004